(this["webpackJsonpchallenge-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpchallenge-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{19:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(31)},24:function(e,t,a){},25:function(e,t,a){},31:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),o=a(17),c=a.n(o),i=(a(24),a(25),a(26),a(8)),s=a(6);var l=function(e){var t=e.index,a=e.length,n=e.category,o=e.difficulty,c=e.question,l=e.correctAns,m=e.incorrectAns,u=e.progressbar,h=e.setScore,d=r.a.useState(""),y=Object(i.a)(d,2),f=y[0],p=y[1],g=r.a.useState(!1),w=Object(i.a)(g,2),E=w[0],b=w[1],v=function(e){var a=t+1;console.log('selected answer "'.concat(e,' , correct ans "').concat(l,'"')),e===l?(p("correct !"),b(!0),h(a)):(p("sorry !"),b(!0))};return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container mt-3 mb-3"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},r.a.createElement("h2",{className:"pl-2 mb-4"}," ","Question ",t+1," of ",a),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"pl-2"},n),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"pl-2 mb-4"},function(e){switch(e){case"hard":return r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":""},"\u2b50\u2b50\u2b50");case"medium":return r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":""},"\u2b50\u2b50");case"easy":return r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":""},"\u2b50");default:return null}}(o)),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h5",{className:"pl-2 mb-4"},c)),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question_options"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},function(e,t){var a=[];a.push(e);for(var n=0;n<t.length;n++)a.push(unescape(t[n]));console.log("all answers",a);var o=a.map((function(e,t){return r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return v(e)},disabled:E}," ",e)}));return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"col ansewrwraper"},o)}(l,m)),E?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"choice"},r.a.createElement("h3",null,f),r.a.createElement(s.b,{to:"/".concat(t+2)},r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return u(t+2)}},"next question"))):null))))},m=a(1),u=a(9);var h=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)(0),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),a=t[0],o=t[1],c=Object(n.useState)(0),h=Object(i.a)(c,2),d=h[0],y=h[1],f=Object(n.useState)(0),p=Object(i.a)(f,2),g=p[0],w=p[1];console.log("que",u);var E=function(e){var t=e/u.length*100;o(t)},b=function(e){y(d+1);var t=d/u.length*100;w(t),console.log(t,e)};return console.log("score",g),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container mt-1"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar bg-success",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(a,"%")},"aria-valuenow":"25","aria-valuemin":"0","aria-valuemax":"100"}))),r.a.createElement(m.c,null,r.a.createElement(m.a,{exact:!0,path:"/"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"option_container"},r.a.createElement("h5",{className:"mb-5"},"Welcome to Quiz"),r.a.createElement(s.b,{to:"/1"},r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return E(1)}},"lets Start !")))),u.map((function(e,t){return r.a.createElement(m.a,{path:"/".concat(t+1)},r.a.createElement(l,{key:t,index:t,length:u.length,category:unescape(e.category),difficulty:e.difficulty,question:unescape(e.question),correctAns:unescape(e.correct_answer),incorrectAns:e.incorrect_answers,progressbar:E,setScore:b}))})),r.a.createElement(m.a,null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"option_container"},r.a.createElement("h3",null," your Score is : ",g),r.a.createElement("h5",{className:"mb-5"},"Restart"),r.a.createElement(s.b,{to:"/"},r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){E(0),w(0)}},"lets Start !"))))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},r.a.createElement("h5",null,"Score: ",g),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar bg-success",role:"progressbar",style:{width:"".concat(g,"%")},"aria-valuenow":"25","aria-valuemin":"0","aria-valuemax":"100"}))))};var d=function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement("header",{className:""},r.a.createElement(s.a,null,r.a.createElement(h,null))))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));c.a.render(r.a.createElement(d,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()}))},9:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')}},[[19,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.20519c1a.chunk.js.map